언제부터 인턴 과정이 있는 거야?
And since when do we have an intern program?
우리는 그렇지 않다. 그리고 키스가 그걸 알게 되면
We don't. And when Keith finds that out,
중요한 사업 교훈이 될 겁니다
it's gonna be a valuable business lesson for him.
뭐?저건 피리 부는 셔츠잖아!
What? Those are the Pied Piper shirts!
당신이 리처드인가요?-네. 네.
Are you Richard? - Yeah. Yes.
알았어, 내가 망쳤어. 우린 지금 뭐하지?
Ok, look, I fucked up. What do we do now?
'우리'가 누구죠?
Who's "we"?
오늘 아침에 당신은 무례하게도 나에게 상기시켜 줬어요.
This morning you rudely reminded me
내가 이 회사의 창립자가 아니었고 지금은
that I wasn't a founder of this company and now
제가 손을 잡고 도와 드릴까요?
you want me to hold your hand and help you out?
난 그렇게 생각 안 해, 언니.
I don't think so, sister.
이 신용 카드는 좋지 않다.
This credit card is no good.
거절하다.
Declined.